dubbed-scene.com 2010-12-10

# Watch Privacy Policy online | Subbed Scene

---|---  
  
Dubbed-Scene.com is committed to protecting your online privacy while providing you with the most useful and enjoyable Web experience possible. While you can use many features of Dubbed-Scene.com anonymously, you are required to provide personal information to gain access to some of our member-only content and services.

How we collect and use personal information

Registering for membership on Dubbed-Scene.com gives you access to all the site’s information and features. The only information required is your e-mail address. 

Our Web site offers image galleries, forums, custom member profiles and other community based features. Please be advised that information posted in these venues becomes public knowledge. 

We offer links to other Web sites. Please note: When you click on links to other Web sites, we encourage you to read their privacy policies. Their standards may differ from ours. 

How we protect your personal information

All personal data you enter on Dubbed-Scene.com is stored on our secure server protected by hardware and software firewalls at a limited access datacenter. 

How we use “cookies”

“Cookies” are small pieces of information that some Web sites store on your computer’s hard drive when you visit them. Like many other Web sites, Dubbed-Scene.com uses cookies to identify members so they don’t have to enter a user ID and password upon each visit. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies but allow you to modify security settings so you can approve or reject cookies on a case-by-case basis. Even if you do not use cookies, you can still access all of the features on our site by logging in manually with each visit. 

What we provide to third parties

While Dubbed-Scene.com does not provide any third-party access to your personal information, we may provide third parties with aggregate statistics about our customers, traffic patterns, and related site information. This data reflects site usage patterns gathered during thousands of customer visits to our Web site each month, but it does not contain behavioral or identifying information about any individual member. 

Dubbed-Scene.com uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our site. This company may use information about your visits to our and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. In addition, we share Web site usage information about visitors to our site with these companies for the purpose of managing and targeting advertisements on our sites. For this purpose, we and our third-party advertising companies note some of the pages you visit on our sites through the use of pixel tags (also called “clear gifs”). In the course of advertisements being served to you, a unique third-party cookie or cookies may be placed your browser. In addition, we use Web beacons, provided by third-party advertising companies, to help manage and optimize our online advertising. Web beacons enable us to recognize a browser’s cookie when a browser visits this site, to learn which banner ads bring users to our Web site and to deliver more relevant advertising. 

If you would like more information about the information collection practices of these third-party advertising companies or would like to know more about your option to not have this information used by these companies or to “opt-out”, click here: 

Obtaining your consent

By using our Web site, you give Dubbed-Scene.com permission to collect information about the pages served to you as an anonymous user for the purpose of calculating aggregate site statistics. If you register at Dubbed-Scene.com you authorize Dubbed-Scene.com to use information you provide to personalize the information we deliver to you and to use your demographic information when calculating aggregate customer data. 

If you are under the age of 18, you must not provide your name, e-mail address, or any other identifying information without the consent of your parent or guardian, or as otherwise provided for by applicable law. Dubbed-Scene.com does not actively market to children, and we never knowingly ask a child under 13 to divulge personal information. 

Any changes to our privacy policy will be posted on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
